DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION SOME SCENES WERE GENERATED USING AI
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED SAFELY
I just got my hooks in.
Where do we go from here?
You can sit comfortably.
Why are you kneeling?
Cut it out, Grandma. You're scaring us.
What were you two doing outside so late at night?
Don't you know there are always people watching on this tiny island?
Today is officially day one for us.
What did you just say?
I like Ms. Hari a lot, ma'am.
Well, I don't like you!
What? Why don't you like him?
He's so frail you had to carry him on your back,
But most importantly, he put you in danger.
If Hari were to go out with someone, :cue
I'd like him to be someone she can rely on.
Grandma, he's also--
Yes, so I'll try harder
To earn your trust, ma'am.
That won't ever happen, so don't even bother trying.
It's getting late, so be on your way now.
I told you, it's no use!
Get up.
That's not exactly
My legs cramped up.
I'm so sorry.
Unbelievable.
- Are you okay? - Mm-hmm.
It's just because she worries about me a lot.
Well, she has every reason to be worried.
But I'm going to show her
That I'm perfectly capable of keeping you safe.
What?
It's a snake.
- A snake in your front yard? - A snake?
- Huh? Why would you grab it? Oh, man - Okay, I got it!
I got it!
- Don't do it. - What's wrong?
- It's kind of cute. Look! - Put it down.
- What's wrong? - Come on. Stop it!
Come on. It's so cute from up close.
Just let it go!
I'll let it go. I'm letting it go now!
Huh? You'll run into a lot of snakes if you go that way.
EPISODE 6 AN UNSPEAKABLE SECRET
I saw the slippers you threw out.
You did that because you didn't want to wear the same ones as me, right?
I'll stop wearing mine, so you can wear those.
You hurt your foot.
Those are the lightest, most comfortable shoes around.
So you bought another pair of these expensive slippers?
Um, yes.
Ah
I threw them out because they were knockoffs.
I was embarrassed and annoyed about that.
Not that Your Highness would have known that knockoffs even existed.
So take these back and get a refund.
I'll pass.
-  Can't you just wear them? - What?
I know your foot is hurting like crazy right now,
And these are the comfiest shoes I've ever worn.
But still, this is too much.
Good morning.
-  Hello. -  Hello.
Are you fighting again?
Not at all.
I told you to get along, but you fight like children.
It's not even noon yet!
It's not what you think.
I just really wanted to get you a pair,
So do whatever you want with them.
See you.
-  Did you sleep well? - Oh, yes.
- How about you, Dr. Do? - Me too.
-  Let me give that a go. - Huh? Oh :cue
Damn.
Here.
It's fine.
You can't even get that open?
Oh.
Ms. Hari, can we talk for a moment?
Sure.
- Excuse me for a moment. - Sure.
Ah Almost walked off with these.
-  Oh, my. Welcome. - Hi.
-  Wait here for just a moment. - I did most of the work getting it open.
Dr. Jiui, a patient's here to see you.
- A patient? -  Hurry.
Hello. How's your tongue?
It's completely healed now.
Please take a seat here.
What brings you here?
I checked my blood sugar levels at the senior center,
- and damn it, I got a reading of 280. - 280?
Did you have anything else besides makgeolli?
Yes, well
I mean, it's the darndest thing, but I didn't have anything to eat.
What the hell?
Okay, this one time, I just had a sip of makgeolli,
- and that was it. - Are you kidding me?
Are you telling me I can't even drink that much?
I can't even.
Okay. I'll stop drinking makgeolli, okay?
I'll also start working out, so don't worry.
I'll take good care of myself and come again next week.
Sure.
Take care.
Dr. Do Jiui sure cares a lot about his patients.
He cares more than my wife!
Let me help you with your payment.
I'm just going to leave today and come back next week.
Okay, have a safe trip back.
INBOX
SEND MESSAGE
Not curious or anything.
Just wondering if it's something I should know.
What did you talk about? Was it about the center?
YUK HARI
Would I seem too petty if I sent this?
Is something wrong with Dr. Chiyeon?
Why did he pull you aside during work hours?
YUK HARI
Dr. Do, my grandma's been approved for the clinical trial.
She'll have tests tomorrow.
Wow, I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations, Ms. Yuk.
Ah
Look at him, trying to play it cool.
He's so adorable.
Hello, you've reached the Public Health Center.
Tomorrow? :cue
The governor said he wants to meet me?
You saved Deokhwa's life.
It sounded like he wanted to commend you for that.
He said you're the perfect symbol of Yeopoong's healthcare modernization.
But it's not like I did it by myself.
Exactly, so when you meet the governor,
Put in a good word for us, okay?
And get him to replace
Why isn't she wearing them? Those shoes must be uncomfortable.
But wouldn't we be short-staffed tomorrow?
We're supposed to visit the Senior Center to treat the grandmas.
Since when did the higher-ups care about any of that?
We'll have to manage on our own somehow.
Mmm
Why won't she wear them?
Gosh, you've been mumbling to yourself nonstop.
What are you mumbling about?
Huh?
It's nothing. Thank you for the meal.
You've barely touched your food again!
You're gonna go and eat gummy worms again, aren't you?
I'm not!
- I'd better not catch you eating them. - You don't even know.
That's why he can't put on any weight.
So frustrating.
I wish I could go with you, but I'm swamped with work at the center.
But they said the tests today won't be too demanding.
- But - Yes?
What's this about a clinical trial all of a sudden?
- Hari, I-- - Grandma.
I heard a super famous professor's in charge of these trials.
On top of that, I heard some patients who were worse off than you
Already saw some improvements.
Okay.
But Hari, the thing is--
Let's go on a trip together once your treatment is over.
There's so much we didn't get to do together
Because I was busy studying and you were busy making money.
- Right. Let's do that. - Mmm.
- The ferry for Yeopoong is now departing. - Goodness, hurry up and go now.
Don't worry about me.
Get going now.
- Have a safe trip, okay? - Okay.
Hurry up and get going.
Huh?
I wonder if Dr. Do managed to board without any issues.
Are you okay?
Sorry?
I just couldn't bring myself to ignore you.
Oh, dear, you look really seasick.
Oh, yes.
What's with that shirt?
You look so sloppy. At least sew it up.
Hmm?
- It's okay. - It's not okay.
You look like a total slob.
I'm only going to wear it here and throw it out.
Only going to wear it here, then throw it out?
A comfy pair of slippers would be good for you.
These are comfy enough. :cue
The ferry bound for Cheongmokdo is now departing.
Oh, my. Hey.
Huh?
Are you okay?
You look pale as a ghost.
Yes, I'm okay.
Hmm
Well then, be on your way.
Would you
Would you like for me to accompany you to the hospital?
W-What for?
Since you were next to me when I was scared,
I figured I'd return the favor.
What's there to be scared of?
Do you take me for a child?
MUJI HOSPITAL
-  Yes, Ms. Yuk. -  Did you arrive in one piece?
I'm at the hospital with your grandmother right now.
- I need to be there by the afternoon, so-- - My grandma?
How's she doing?
Is she all right?
I'll get back to you once the tests are done.
Okay. Give me a call.
Okay.
Are you nervous?
What's there to be nervous about?
They'll be testing you to see how you respond to the treatment
Before you undergo the clinical trials.
It's a simple test, so there's nothing to be afraid of.
So I might really undergo clinical trials once they finish testing me today?
What would that be like?
Well, I think
Forget it. Don't even bother answering.
I know you'll tell me that everything will be fine.
That everything will be fine.
I'm sure the hospital staff will give you a rundown.
But the clinical trial process won't be a walk in the park.
If you were to suffer any side effects
It might put you in even greater danger.
Cancer's never easy on the patient.
- Mmm - That's why
If it's too hard, you can say so.
Okay.
All done.
Apply some pressure on it, and once the bleeding stops, put this on.
We're going to do an ECG now, so please stay seated here for a moment.
- Okay. - Right.
:cue
Ms. Oh Mija, let me take you to get that ECG now.
Ms. Oh Mija!
Ms. Oh Mija, are you here?
Excuse me.
Didn't Ms. Oh Mija go inside to get examined?
I told her to sit here and wait, but I don't see her.
- Uh P-Please wait for just a moment. - Oh
The number you've dialed cannot be reached at this time.
Is my grandma doing all right?
DR. DODO
Do give me a call when it's over.
WHAT IS AN ADVANCE DIRECTIVE?
A LEGAL DOCUMENT STATING AN ADULT'S WISHES
REGARDING END-OF-LIFE CARE
What are you doing here?
Goodness, what is the matter with you?
I told you I'd take care of it myself,
So please just leave me alone.
Oh, my.
Ma'am.
If you're scared, it's okay to tell me that you're scared.
I told you I'm not scared.
I also tried to hide the fact that I was scared of the sea,
But Ms. Hari found out.
But I actually felt relieved
Once it was out in the open.
I could be as scared as I wanted.
So it's okay to be afraid.
I had no intention of going through with the clinical trials to begin with.
I also know that I don't have much time left.
Five years after I received chemotherapy,
They declared that I was cancer-free.
Hari and I hugged each other and cried so much, saying it was all over
But goodness
Turns out cancer is incredibly stubborn.
It won't ever relent until it's taken everything from you.
Going back and forth to the hospital
To receive the painful treatment was scary,
And the thought of death was also terrifying.
But what scared me the most
:cue
Was spending my final moments looking like an empty shell,
Neither alive nor dead.
I just want to keep going about my day as I always have
And eventually die as Hari's grandmother.
That is my wish.
That's awfully selfish of me, isn't it?
You must think I'm a terrible grandmother.
If Hari were to find out, she'd be devastated.
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
Not at all.
You
Must have been so lonely.
That's what I'm thinking.
You must've been terrified, dealing with this alone.
Yes, Ms. Yuk.
They're still examining her.
I'll get back to you once it's over.
Okay.
I LOVE YEOPOONG
Hello.
- You're Dr. Do Jiui, right? - Yes.
I see. Right this way.
Oh. Hello. This way.
Oh, my.
Dr. Do Jiui.
When they heard that I'd be meeting you,
The reporters were dying of curiosity
- Over here. Please look this way. - and came all this way.
Just act natural and try to relax.
- It's not natural at all. - Relax.
Please look this way too.
KO CHANGMOK WILL LEAD
YEOPOONG-GUN'S HEALTHCARE MODERNIZATION
The child was having trouble breathing due to acute epiglottitis.
We had to get her to a hospital quickly, so we took the village chief's boat,
And all the medical staff on the scene
Did all they could to save the child's life.
Did you receive any help from the county office?
The county office--
Just tell them what happened. No need to hold back.
Well, the
I see our good doctor's really nervous.
I, Ko Changmok, will do everything in my power
To fully support these islands
So that they can bring any patient back to life right away. Okay?
That's why we're renovating 20 helipads
In remote locations throughout the county.
:cue
Goodness, you've done wonders for Yeopoong-gun's public image, Dr. Do Jiui.
Now then, a toast to Dr. Do Jiui!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Thank you, Dr. Do.
MS. YUK HARI
- We're counting on you. - Let me pour you one.
- Oh, my. - Let me pour you one.
The number you've called
- cannot be reached at this time. - I guess he's busy.
I miss him.
Make sure you call me even if it's late.
I miss you.
Hello?
I'm sorry. Did I wake you up?
No, you didn't.
Why are you up so soon, though?
What time is your ferry?
The earliest one.
The earliest one?
Oh It must have left already, though.
Can you come outside your house for a moment?
I miss you.
Outside my house?
Dr. Do!
What the heck?
I'm sorry I couldn't pick up last night.
I came as soon as I could. I waited at the port for the first ferry.
You didn't have to do that.
- You must be exhausted. - I missed you.
And how did you get along with my grandma? Did you manage okay on the ferry?
Yes, I suppose.
Don't you worry.
My grandma always lets me have my way, so if I keep telling her I like you,
I'm sure she'll change her mind.
Ms. Yuk.
I'll be by your side, no matter what happens. Okay?
I'll do the same.
GOVERNOR OF YEOPOONG-GUN
REASSIGNMENT ORDER FOR PUBLIC HEALTH DOCTOR DO JIUI
"Saving her life wouldn't have been possible
Without Governor Ko Changmok's help"?
"PH doc Do Jiui extends his gratitude to Governor Ko Changmok, :cue
Who supported their cause in every way possible--"
I didn't take you for that kind of guy.
You cozy up to powerful people, huh?
- No, wait -  Judging by that photo,
People might think the two of you were best buds.
I didn't take you for a man of such ambition.
They twisted my words.
I talked about our center a lot, okay?
- I can't even - Yes. I'm sure you did.
That Ko Changmok, damn it.
Is there a doctor here?
A doctor! Come out here!
Goodness, what's this about?
- This is going to sting. - Okay.
Hang in there. Keep those eyes shut.
Holy hell.
How on earth did this happen?
He fell over at a construction site.
They've been rushing this project,
So someone was bound to get injured.
What's this I hear about an accident?
What happened?
What kind of accident?
Jeez, how useless could you be?
You took the money, mucked up your job
And now here you are, slacking off.
I'm sorry, sir.
How the hell could you say that? A man is injured.
That's why you lot should have stuck to the safety protocols!
How are you going to make up for all the time lost because of this?
- How? - A man's been injured!
Who cares about time lost? Huh?
I care about the time lost, you oaf.
Time is money.
You'd better not use this as an excuse to spout some crap like,
"We're out of funds," or "We need more time."
I'll kill you all if you do.
Jeez, we're already running behind schedule.
- What a nightmare. - I'm gonna kill this asshole.
Hey! You heartless bastard.
Don't you even care that a man's injured? Huh?
Let go of me. Have you completely lost it?
Yeah, I've completely lost it! What choice do I have but to go crazy?
I told you, didn't I?
That we'd end up dying if you kept rushing us.
- What are you all doing? Stop him! - No one try to stop me!
-  Please - I'm going to kill you,
- then kill myself today. - Okay!
All right, man. Then how about this? I give you more time
I'll kill you!
What the
That's enough. There are patients here.
I'm the one who was attacked!
I'm the victim here!
It seems the accident has caused a lot of ill will between you.
Why don't you make up here?
Listen. I should be suing you for this.
But I'll let it slide since we're pressed for time.
What are you still doing here? Scram.
- Why, you - Hey
Stop. That's enough.
You should get going.
Right. Thank you so much, Doctor. :cue
- Jeez. - Come on.
Let's go.
I can't let you leave just yet, sir.
What now?
I told you last time, didn't I?
Interfering with medical care is an aggravated crime.
Damn it.
Why are you telling me that?
I'm the one who was attacked!
If this ever happens again
I won't let it slide.
Wow, this is unbelievable.
So what if you won't let it slide? What will you do about it?
What will you do?
Hey, hey, hey.
- Dr. Hyeon. - Let go.
Our doctor tends to spout nonsense when he gets agitated.
He's just like that.
Nonsense
They're just kids. I'll give them a good scolding.
You don't want to get into a fight.
That's the second time she's saved your life.
Strike three, and you're really going to get it!
You're the bigger man.
They're just immature kids.
Thanks as always.
- Goodness. -  Damn it.
Have a safe trip back, okay?
I told you to just suck it up, and you couldn't even do that?
I don't know who he's connected to,
But he forced his way into becoming the head of the fisheries co-op.
He's got the village's finances on a tight leash
So all of Pyeondongdo is basically at his mercy!
Rub him the wrong way, and we could really end up in big trouble!
You're killing me!
So
Are you saying I was in the wrong?
You doctors won't have to deal with this once you leave after a year.
What?
Once you leave, that'll be it for you. But those of us left behind will suffer.
But Dr. Chiyeon also did what he did for our center.
- No, what I meant to say is -  I understand your concerns.
I was out of line.
Dr. Hyeon
Come on, Doctor. What I meant to say was
Why's he getting so worked up about that?
It's not like you lied about them leaving.
The PH docs were the first to always draw a line between us, weren't they?
I mean, think back to Dr. Do's interview.
Ms. Hari was the one who saved him,
But he didn't even say a single word about her.
- I'm okay with-- - Hey!
I usually eat three slices.
May I take the two remaining slices?
- Sure. - Then I'll get going now.
Careful.
- Take care. - My throat is parched.
- Can I also take a soda? -  Sure.
See you.
Ms. Yuk Hari.
I suggest you pick a side and stick to it.
Okay. :cue
Whoa, Dr. Yong.
From now on, I'm just going to do my job and nothing else,
Since I'll be leaving anyway!
I'm on your side, by the way.
How about you, Dr. Do?
What?
I'm asking whose side you're on, okay?
Are you with the PH docs having ramyeon, or the nurses having pizza?
Pick a side.
I'm on your side.
- Right? - Yeah.
This is so frustrating.
The PH docs feel like we really let them down, right?
Yes. Kind of.
The nurses must also be really angry. Right?
- Yes. Kind of. - Oh
If people found out we were dating in secret,
- the fallout would be catastrophic. - Very.
I'm going outside, so count to 100 before you come.
One hundred?
LUCKY SUPERMARKET
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten
It's like you two don't even see me!
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
One hundred!
- Go. - Hurry up and go.
I'm okay. You should go.
It's time to order next year's medicinal ingredients.
If you doctors need anything, we need to submit a form for it.
So please go over your patient charts carefully and turn them in.
Please submit these by this week.
Sure.
But how are we supposed to know which ingredients we'll be needing next year
When we'll be leaving soon?
Well
It's what every doctor before you did before leaving.
I guess I didn't know since I'm leaving soon anyway.
Well, now that you know, do it.
No! I can't do it!
What the
Why are you guys fighting? Huh?
Gosh!
I'm sorry for yelling.
I'm also sorry. I didn't mean it, either.
We received a fax.
Huh?
What is it?
Dr. Do.
It says you're to report to Yeopoong-gun starting tomorrow.
NOTICE OF REASSIGNMENT
"Notice of reassignment"?
"required to report to the Yeopoong-gun public health center"? :cue
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER DIRECTOR CHOI HYANGMI
Hello?
Ms. Choi, this is Dr. Do Jiui, the PH doc from Pyeondongdo.
I just received a notice of reassignment.
I guess the governor really took a liking to you, Dr. Do,
Judging by how quickly he summoned you.
It's just that I'm having a hard time accepting such a sudden reassignment.
Dr. Do Jiui,
Any qualms you have about the matter are irrelevant.
You are a civil servant and a soldier.
If you don't follow orders, you will face severe penalties.
I get that you're emotionally invested in the island.
But you're not from there anyway.
Just think of this as an early farewell.
I'll see you tomorrow at Yeopoong-gun.
Dr. Do, are you busy today?
I know that you're disappointed in me.
But since this'll be your last day here, we should have a meal together.
I know that I'm a coward.
Hey, why would you say that?
But what other choice did I have? Huh?
Any trouble we stir up with that sorry lot would only end up harming our patients.
That's why I did what I did.
I wasn't scolding you because you would be leaving soon.
Absolutely not!
So if you hold any grudges against me, let them go before you leave.
Here
I prepared this as soon as I got the call from you, Ms. Sinhye.
Right.
You asked me to prepare it with the freshest catch.
So I went there myself to get my hands on these.
Well done.
I wanted to serve up my best dish.
Thank you.
You'd never find a dish like this on the mainland.
It's going to blow your mind once you try it.
It's delicious.
What a relief.
Eat your fill, Dr. Do.
Eat up.
Yes, eat.
You're drunk. Stop drinking.
Pull yourself together.
Why did you drink so much?
Why do you care if I drink or not?
I drank because I'm frustrated. So what?
Are you that frustrated that Dr. Jiui's leaving?
Everyone leaves.
They all do eventually.
Let go of me. :cue
Hey.
I'd like to ask you something.
Why do you keep wearing such uncomfortable shoes?
Why do you care?
It bothers me.
Then just take them back.
Pretend it never happened.
Taking back a gift doesn't change the fact that I gave it to you.
We both know exactly what happened that day!
Stop running your mouth.
You talk way too much.
I'm going to say it.
What happened that day
I liked it.
I also liked the things we talked about, and
My point is I definitely liked it.
What use is any of that?
You'll be leaving eventually.
Isn't that why you don't bother to sew up your clothes?
Because you'll be leaving soon anyway?
Is that what's been bothering you?
I mean, if you care so much about the holes in my shirt,
Why won't you wear the slippers I got you?
Because they're wasted on me!
A country bumpkin like me doesn't have the guts to strut around
Wearing something so valuable on my feet!
Did you have a lot to drink?
Yes.
Because I'm happy.
We couldn't have asked for a better outcome.
You won't have to cross the ocean you fear so much anymore.
And we'll be free to go on all the dates we want on the mainland,
Unlike our current arrangement here.
Man, this is great.
- Are you really okay with it? - Huh?
No.
Dr. Do,
Please don't leave me.
Stay by my side.
I wish you would stay by my side.
You're really drunk.
Stay by my side. :cue
You all said you wouldn't come see me off.
Well, the port just happens to be on my route to work,
So I'm just standing here to take a quick breather.
Don't mind me.
- I was also just passing by. -  Mm-hmm.
Why are you acting like you didn't come out here on purpose?
You're so weird.
Dr. Do!
Deokhwa!
Careful!
We got back to the island after she was discharged yesterday,
But we didn't get a chance to stop by.
Here's a gift for you, Dr. Do.
It's for me?
I'm also going to become a superhero who saves people's lives, just like you.
Thank you, Deokhwa.
- You'll come visit, right? - I will.
I'll get going now.
I'll get going.
The ferry bound for Yeopoong will be departing soon.
To all remaining passengers, please board the ferry right away.
Let's go back now, okay?
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER DO JIUI
Can you turn to the right for us?
Smile, please.
Make a bigger heart. Bigger!
- Okay. - Give us a cheek heart too.
A cheek heart.
-  Thank you. - A cheek heart. While smiling.
The other side too. Both sides. That's great.
That's great.
Okay, that's enough for today.
- Thank you, everyone. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Dr. Do, go grab a meal then come back.
We'll be having a PR shoot for the modernization initiative.
But
Wasn't I transferred to Yeopoong-gun to serve as a PH doc?
How am I going to treat patients if I'm busy taking photos?
I haven't even had the time to go over the patients' charts yet.
You don't have to treat any patients.
What else would a doctor do?
You're due to join the governor tomorrow for his interview.
You've had your hair done, right?
Hmm. Here's your schedule for tomorrow.
DR. DO JIUI'S SCHEDULE FOR OCTOBER 1
- Let's go, Ms. Choi. -  Okay. :cue
Man, that tastes like crap.
Do Jiui!
Having fun on the mainland?
We haven't even been apart for that long, but I miss you already!
I said, I miss you!
You're here early.
Ms. Yuk.
Can we talk for a moment?
Why? Did something happen?
Dr. Do Jiui.
Here's your schedule for this week's press tour.
Let me know if you need anything.
It's one interview after another. Man, this is so
Are you busy?
Give me a call, Ms. Yuk.
YEOPOONG ILBO YEOPOONG'S PERSON OF THE MONTH
HEALTHCARE MODERNIZATION IN UNDERSERVED ISLANDS
Why'd they put this in my room?
I'm so sick of it all.
MS. YUK HARI
Ms. Yuk, is something wrong?
I'm worried about you.
"I'd like to impart a proposal to you."
"Impart"?
"I'd like to make a proposal."
:cue
With the esteemed Dr. Do Jiui by my side,
I'd just really like to try,
To try as hard as hell,
To bring the modernization of healthcare in Yeopoong-gun into reality.
Thank you for sharing your dedication
To achieving healthcare modernization.
But judging by the look on the doctor's face,
It seems he's got something to say.
Would you mind sharing it with us?
I'd like to make a proposal.
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
What? At the port?
Yes, I understand.
- It's a fall injury patient. Get ready. - Okay.
Dr. Chiyeon!
We have a fall injury patient at the port!
- A fall injury? - Yes. Hurry.
DANGER DO NOT APPROACH
Excuse us, move aside please.
I'm sorry. Please move aside.
Let's flush the wound.
- Some saline please. - Okay.
We need a splint to hold his ankle.
Okay.
It's an open fracture.
We'll need some clean cloth for an elastic bandage.
BONE EXPOSED THROUGH SKIN
ELASTIC BANDAGE
Please hold him down. Setting the bone now.
It's been realigned.
- More saline please. - Okay.
Every half hour, keep tightening and loosening the tourniquet for five minutes.
Yes, I understand. We'll take it from here.
- Okay. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you. - Are you doing okay?
Yes.
Oh, my. Good work, everyone.
- Well done, Dr. Jiui. - Thanks.
Goodness.
Huh?
Wait, Dr. Jiui. What are you doing here?
My transfer's been canceled.
What?
I see.
So that's how it is.
ON-SITE ISSUES
BRINGING YOU THE NEWS LIVE ON THE SCENE
Like you said, Governor,
I don't want island residents to think
That death is the only option when they get sick.
Of course!
So please,
Send me back to Pyeondongdo.
As a doctor, I shouldn't be in front of a camera
"WHAT'S HE SAYING?"
But in front of patients.
Mr. Do Jiui's remark reminds us of the true purpose
Of the public health system
Which sends doctors to underserved regions in place of military service.
That concludes our weekly on-site issue segment.
Well, I'll be.
To think he'd dare to screw me over like that in front of the reporters.
I'm sorry, sir.
I won't let him get away with this.
Just wait and see how I deal with him!
That
You're dead.
I won't let you get away with this!
Damn it.
And that
Is why I'm back for good.
I won't be leaving anytime soon.
So he told you to tell him what you want,
- and you asked him to send you back here? - Yeah. :cue
Why'd you answer Pyeondongdo, of all places?
You should have said Gyeonggi-do.
You really crack me up, Dr. Yong.
You didn't even get the joke.
He should have asked to be sent to a different island?
Gyeonggi-do's not actually an island.
Is something wrong?
Are you shocked because I suddenly came back?
Why was it so hard to reach you?
I know you were busy, but you could have at least checked in.
I was really worried about you.
I thought something might have happened.
Are you mad at me?
Why didn't you tell me
That my grandma
Gave up on life?
Ms. Yuk, well
I'm going to
I'm going to convince her to change her mind.
I'd be nothing without my grandma.
So, Dr. Do
Help me change her mind.
You can't do it?
Because you're a doctor who has to respect his patients' wishes?
Can't you do it for me, not as a doctor
But as my boyfriend?
I'm sorry.
CAN'T YOU DO IT FOR ME, NOT AS A DOCTOR
BUT AS MY BOYFRIEND?
THIS IS THE MOMENT THEIR ROMANCE TRULY TAKES OFF
RUNNING LINES UNTIL THE VERY LAST MOMENT
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
It would have been better if you hadn't returned.
I have nothing to say to you, Dr. Do.
Can you stay by Hari's side for just a little while longer?
I would have chosen otherwise.
Are you getting ready to die?
Why are you sorting things out?
Oh, no!
Yes.
We need a medical chopper!
-  Patient shows no signs of life. -  You can't leave us like this!
Translated by Yoon Hyuk Park